Welcome to AI Plus Nov Smartphones
presents India's God Latent Quick
Delivery Partner Flipkart Minutes Protein
Partner Avatar Protein Fragrance Partner
Wildstone & District Make plans
and go out let's go
[cheering]
this [ __ ] now and are we ready to start the
show
we have a banger panel for you guys we're gonna go crazy make noise
for Tanmay
[screaming] Bhatt
[cheering]
Bull P
Rahul Dua [cheering
] and Karan Aujiya [cheering] [cheering] [cheering
]
let's go
[cheering]
make so [ __ ] [
cheering] [applause]
what a panel man what a [ __ ] panel what a
thing bhaiya Karan bhai thank you so much for coming
man thank you guys thank
you bhai thank you for having me anything paani wani
kuch lenge aap
nahi I am right bhaiya it's
free in our show [laughter]
then  I will take it brother [laughs]
but Karan bhai.  Thank you so much for coming
man.  You are truly a legend and I can't believe
you are here, brother.
Or Man Me Too.  I don't know if I did the
right thing coming here.  But I have just arrived.
So
no you are the funniest Punjabi on the panel
today.
But right now Karan Bhai is with Virat Kohli.  And right
now it's late and pay.
What next?  Tanmay, will you react
?  [laughs]
Sometimes in life you have to downgrade.
[laughs]
Also Karan Aujla has actually come from Dubai
for the show or that's true all the way from
Dubai.  Thank you so much for doing that.
Thank you brother.  I could have come from anywhere.
No, usually people go to Dubai after its release.
[laughter]
My flight is booked, bro.  After this I am going to
leave.  But friend, I love you so much
, Karan Bhai.  Love you.
Thank you so much for coming man.  I can't
believe you really.  And I am really a big fan
of Tanmay Bhai.  Thank you.
[Cheering voice]
Come on man, you were just about to win me over,
man.
But people call Karan Aujla Geeta Di
Machine.  That's right.  Karan Bhai,
keep a water machine in your show also.  [laughter]
No, that water is needed.  You have to go
to the ATM machine and then [laughs] get water.
Okay, tell me, look who is the FIR machine
[laughs]
Okay, whoever doesn't know this water story,
I had shows here in Bombay
and it was a Holi event and
just to give the context, imagine there was
no water in the Holi show
[laughs]
Okay friend, it was not my fault,
why should I name the team right now, come on, it was whose fault it was, there was
less water there, the water that was available was very
expensive, so I have to hear this till today.
So but after that we did We Came Back Strung
Mumbai 2.0 and a lot of people liked
it.   Did
you guys go to his Bombay show
?  [laughter]
What is this?
My placement is also very good.
Try it brother is better than avitaur.
[laughter]
It's zero.  It's named after Rahul Dua's
India Door Ses.
[laughs]
Sorry friend
no it's right it's right it's correct at least you are
accurate this time [laughs]
yes PK let's see is
this PV is sitting friend I
know about it there are so many scenes [laughs]
hmm it's actually pretty [ __ ] [laughs]
which will load later let's go
this PK only wrote it he didn't sleep it's not a
storm [laughs]
butter applause for Karan Ojalai what [ __ ]
guy come on [cheering voice] you are also
Tanmay Bhat in the house
but so happy to be here I am a big fan of
your music friend thank you
what's your favourite song |
ah my favorite song i love one of the new
songs take it is i love |
Yes what you have been doing in your career
also I
know you love 52 times because you have been
behind it so
friend chale case to case [laughs]
but thank you so much for coming Tanmay I love
you so much we also have along with Geeta di
machine brand work di machine
accha yeh dekh raha
khud six brands leke baitha hua hai [laughs]
tu hai
mera legal fees wo
same show YouTube Netflix dono pe [laughs]
aur brand di
haujla ke show se zyada sale out toh samay rahna hai bhai.
[laughs] I have to
earn a little bit now, don't I?
But Gullin' How Are You Feeling?  You know
Gullan is the biggest fan of Karan Bhai on the
panel.
True.
Just an hour ago he decorated himself Just
to be here for real.  She was doing what you were doing
for 1 hour, friend.
[laughter]
Whatever you were doing.  By the way, we had the
same makeup artist.  So it is
not his fault.
[laughs]
So it's like desi bling happened
with us too.
No, Gulin looks very beautiful.  Thank you so much
for coming.   Thank you
brother.
And we also have Rahul Dua.
Thanks brother.  Thank you.  Thank you.
Thank you very much.  Thank you.  Thank you before someone makes a joke.
Thank you so much for having me here.
I am very happy to be here.
No friend, I was going to promote you.
He has just made a show.  Its name
is Pitch Please.
Or it's like it's a play on the word [ __ ]
please.  You took out the B and drank it.  Pitch you
get it?  [laughs]
So to enjoy one hour of true comedy
you can go to Rahul Show.  Happening All
Across the World Now Apparently.  No [laughs]
no not happening anywhere anymore.  I have
closed it on my own will.  Unlike some
shows.
But how much do you love
Ojala friend.  Come on.  Brother, brother, I am a
big fan.  I actually listen to his songs
and I also do in-depth analysis.
Like
your lyrics are very good.  You are
called Geeta's machine.
But I am telling you that even if you make it a little slow, it will be fine.
Because you should listen to your lyrics yourself first
because in the first line you write that the
Jat has either drunk or taken money
and after a minute you say that you are
telling the girl that I am not time for you otherwise I do
n't have time to sleep.
So first you're saying either I drink
or I go to sleep.  And now again
after a minute you are saying that I am
not able to sleep.  Oh brother, I do it like this.
So to enjoy one hour
of such annie [cheering voice] then you can go
to Rahul for our show happening
nearest 15 seater around you alright.
So now before we fight here again like
any Karan was concert ah let's give a
shout out to our brand AI Plus phone.  This
is the phone that's sponsoring our show.  And
I have seen a lot in your show.  Hey
[laughter] man, listen to it.   There's a
lot of theft in your show.  I have
seen it.  [laughter]
Right?
So you appeal to your audience to buy
the Ai Plus phone because this is the phone no one
wants to steal.  [laughter]
Now even its founder won't be able to sleep.
Brother sponsored the wrong show.  But should we
begin India's got latent let's go
[cheering voice]
make some not the first sweet in Hartman
sweet in Hartman
guys make some nose yaar come on
[music]
[screaming voice]
that was sex so f [laughter]
Jab ye shuru kiya udikm aisa laga lift me
enter kar gaye udikm
bhai as the only musician on the panel what did you think
about it Tanmay Bhat [laughter]
I got enjoyed it man.  That was amazing, that was
really good man.  But do you think
it's good [laughs]
Welcome to India Got Leader and Karan
Geeta without a machine.  [laughter] It
was great, man.  Why did you learn this in this country
?  [laughs] I
think I had a bit of an itch to
finger some instrument like that.
I will give you one like this, give me, I will
take the money for it, this is your protein for you
brother, take this [encouraging voice]
put this in your pocket and put it in your mouth later
Karan bhai, do you know how to play any instrument
brother, I don't play anything
but I want to say something Karan bhai,
I have met you before,
you might remember that ad shoot,
ok, ok, you were there, did
you enjoy it [laughter]
[encouraging voice]
no friend brother, he plays well friend [laughter]
thank you brother, thank you, thank you so what happened
there [laughter] no, he came, we were playing,
after that he left, he didn't even talk that much, didn't even
take a photo, nothing, hey friend,
look, you are on the show today friend, what a thing
[laughter] there will be no photo today also
brother brother wrote I have almost choked a
classmate by tangling him with my bare
hands.  Didn't he put it in my mouth?
No, that's because I didn't learn anything at that time.
No brother, what happened?  You almost choked a
classmate.
Karan bhai [laughs]
This guy makes love songs, brother.
So what happened brother that you almost
choked a classmate by strangling him.
What did he do?
So we had a fight and I got really
angry.  And I don't know what happened.  The next
thing I know, I'm like pushing him to the
wall and choking him, it's like trying to kill
him. I was so scared after that that I thought I'd have died.
Maybe this wouldn't have happened. If you were in jail, maybe not.
Yes, maybe not. [laughs]
Bro, let's avoid these topics. The
police are very strict there. The police are very
strict here too.
[laughs] The
police come here in 30 minutes.
Yes, I know. [laughs] If you order from Flipkart, the
police can come in 10 minutes.
[encouraging voice] The
police have come, the police have come,
Paaji, some cases have happened to you. I also get cases
sometimes.
What have you done? Tell me, I have
n't faced anything as bad as what happened to you.
Why did you? I never
asked this. Would you rather do this or that?
[laughter]
What did you do?
I said, I'm [ __ ] Abru, there was a
case against him,
and what, man. There was a
and what, what did you do?
Then what did you do, brother? [laughter]
[encouraging voice] man
Gul, a case has been filed against you till now.
I don't even need it brother.  I would like to
tell the editor, brother, please check the edit.  They don't
see this.  [laughter]
[cheering]
I don't want to play.
Rahul Bhai, you tell me half a joke.
[laughs]
Dude, whoever cracked the joke in the last season,
after H for Habit, he has gone to H for Hawalaat, that
for one hour [laughs]
I love you dude,
yes I wish I could say the same
Gurleen Pannu dude, may be you can only abuse him now dude, no dude, no,
I just want to hear him sing, he has
also written singing,
some songs are without copyright, sing some
without copyright brother,
yes any of his songs brother, do you have the rights of
your songs,
yes brother,
sing that one, then sing Goat Goat [laughs]
Diamond Naal, that is Diljit, ok ok ok ok ok, he has written it,
I have written it, aren't you happy aunty,
that was the most,
brother, these rappers just keep writing each other's songs,
dude [laughs]
Paaji, who has written Brown Rang?
This is the one that I just put the cup on
its right side.
No, that's not me either.  [laughter]
So what did you sing about then?
Cannot sleep.
Cannot sleep.  Bhai sleep no any of Karan
Aujla songs?
Friend, don't sing my praises.
Dude, please dude.
No.
Someone should come without auto tune.  [laughs] I
love your lips, man.  [laughs] It
says Mangalorean cuisine is the best
in India.  Now that's a fight here.  Delhi
girl here.  There is a Kashmiri boy here.
Canada Visa Here.  [laughs] He
is a Punjabi, brother.
So a Punjabi cuisine is so good.   It is
Delhi cuisine.  Have
you eaten Kashmiri food?  What happens in Bangalore is that there are Shetty
people.  There are Birwaz.   The
Barrys are Muslims and the Goins are
Catholics.  So every culture has its own
cuisine style and when you
come to the South, it becomes such a pot of Puri and you get such
exotic flavours.  My mouth is
watering, man.  Look, let's give them
sex.  [laughter]
I love you, man.  This joke has to be said after it is done.
[laughter]
not a joke storm [laughter]
alright makes noise for sweet and hearty
man [cheering]
[applause]
time to score him brother let's start
from Rahul Dua
brother I would like to give you number nine
thank you 10 number from my end brother
thank you thank you [laughter]
I will give six number one
arre you will give six number you have given six six number
friend.  It doesn't happen like this, friend.  He
puts a lot in his mouth, man.  [laughter]
So I'm also telling you, it's number six,
man.  So your average is eight.
Oh my god.
Wow brother, what confidence you have.
Brother, you gave 10 on 10 yourself.  Good
brother.
Thank you so much for joining.  I guess.  Thank
you.
Thank you [appreciation] so much.
Make Some Next Act Vijendra Rajak.
[Music]
Brother, please don't fall.
This is how people try to see Karan Aujla show
in the standing section.  [laughter]
Brother, my ass is bursting.  My ass is bursting.   It is
also visible from behind.   Pull up your
pants.  [laughter]
Sorry friend
[applause] [music]
brother [applause]
hey brother I
thought it would fly in the air now [laughter]
oh my god friend nice wow friend guys
clapping friend
[music]
[laughter]
what a thing [encouraging voice]
[applause]
brother crazy brother
so you do something are you in some circus paaji
you are
not I am an acrobatic person by the way I am also a dance choreographer
I have also done reality shows
India is good talent you did not become famous after India talent
yes there is so much talent in India where is there a riot it is nonsense you have come
here to do it
[encouraging voice]
[applause] ok ok
you have written I am married for two years.
Happily married.  Happily happy at his house,
this is my happy.  This happened after 2 years.
This must have happened due to rotating the tyre.   No no,
after marriage I suddenly came to know
that I did not elope with her.
Where did my wall go?  Where did you run away?  [laughter] I'm
not running away.
She turned around and went along.
No, she ran away with me.
She took it away running away.   She ran away and took it away.
Ma'am, please come on stage, ma'am, I had to
chase her away. You do
n't even have a tube in your tyre [laughs]
Mike ma'am, what is your name?
My Manju Rajak,
Manju ji, Manju ji, you chased her away.
Yes,
tell me the story, how did you do it?
We were in a relationship for a month and I had to get
married. She also had to get married. It was
n't that I didn't want to get married, but the fact was that
my family wasn't agreeing, so I
thought what should I do, what should I do? I
told her that her family wasn't agreeing, so
she got nervous out of tension. She said, no,
what happened? I said, come to the sugarcane shop, I want to meet her. I met her while
sitting in the car, she
said, didi, let's go home, I mean, my sister, we went home, we went there and
said, we want to get married. I said, we want to get married, we want to
waste time. We were roaming around playing and
jumping. We want to get married. It's just a little hard work.
I said, we will do it slowly. We have to get married
today, otherwise we won't do it.
You said,
yes, I had to get married. I ran away
from home because I need
money for the wedding. Now we will do it
from the temple also.  He
said that it costs money to get the certificate and a complaint was lodged there.  The
police are after me here.
My brother was picked up.  Picked everyone up.
Why?   He
said that he forcibly kidnapped the girl.
And he chased me away.  [laughter] That's what
I was going to say.
Now I called my friend.  Brother, please give me the money.
I need it.  He is saying that I do
n't have money to eat the jailer.  I said I will
feed you in jail.  [laughter] Give me the money.
A jailer is stuck around my neck.
So how did you gain so much confidence in him to marry him within a month
?  Their
nature and meaning is that when they
see a person, they get that feeling, hi, I mean, that feeling, and I get on top
[laughs], don't you have no
balance,
wow, they keep you on their
eyelids, yes,
then they take you around, they keep an eye on you
[laughs]
[encouraging voice] right now,
in the hotel, there's no gate in the washroom, I
mean, there's no latch,
yes, where is this habit, at least
check it a little, I mean, what happens,
this happens at my house too, like when I go to the washroom, what are you doing, put it back,
I said, come inside, both of us sit
half-half [laughs]
I left you here, leave you in the washroom, I am
here, I am not going anywhere,
you had to come to the show alone, I will
also come, so do you not trust them,
this
trust is there, but there is one thing that remains, that means it is
important to be around them, to be around them,
so cute friend, there is
one thing that I cannot live alone, I cannot
live without them at all, this thing
because their family members blocked me, I
mean, they thought that [laughs]
[praise] I am saying
and  No one is saying that there is no one left.
Manju ji, you seem like such a romantic type.  Does
he ever do anything romantic for you
?   I have
done a lot.
Yes, tell me something romantic that he has done.
Meaning, by placing it here and there, I turned my
heart.  [laughter]
Your goal in life.  You have to
take your wife to Maldives.   Why so
?
Why is it such a big dream of yours to
go to Maldives?  I like it, I mean we will
see it in the videos, otherwise we will see,
both of you are very happy, right? Yes,
come on, play this show, I will sponsor you both tickets to the mall
[encouraging voice] [applause]
what water friend water water water [laughter]
play water
brother so sweet of you brother applaud brother friend brother's friend,
look friend, sometimes we become
very ungrateful, so man
and why not if you can do something with this
beautiful this beautiful couple.
Thank you sir.
Yes, you are getting it because of your wife.
You have no [laughs] in this.
Because of this, we get everything nowadays.   You do
n't have to take the wheel with you there.
[laughter] I did
n't want to hit the wheel.
Ok.  Yes sir.  [laughter]
If you don't mind, my brother.  Where is
your next show?
Sir, not right now.  I mean, there are a lot of
problems going on in my life.
What happened?  Right now, only the two of us are living.  That
means Bhavi and everyone else separated from my house too.  Right now
I also live on rent.
So right now we are doing both and the debt has become very
high.  Borrowing from here and
borrowing from there has created a problem.  I still
brought my phone by mortgaging it.   Can
you tell me how much is your loan
?   Let me tell you.
Tell me.
Yes, please tell me.
Sir, mine is worth ₹1 lakh.
I am out.
[laughter]
Paaji, it wo
n't be that much Paaji, I will try, but I
hope you get so many shows through this that
you earn 12 lakhs like this brother, Paaji, just
look at the camera once and say
please book my show
[laughter]
[applause] Just say it
once Paaji, please book my show,
not Paaji, please friend [laughter]
[nasal voice]
yes,
give them two AI F's friend, yes I can give it, I will
give it in the end,
their F is mortgaged, your F is also mortgaged,
not mine brother,
their F is mortgaged, their F is mortgaged, so it is
broken, right,
you kept the F mortgaged, why, first tell me
sir, I had to come, I mean, my expenses, like I have
not come here at all, I don't have rent yet, I have given
you the money for coming,
yes, I have given it, like I have to leave from here,
we will pay for that too, brother, we don't give just one ticket, so what do
you think, Karan Bhai, I will send you the mobile
[laughter]
so we will take care of the return too, friend.   That's
for you.
Thank you sir.   Thank
you.
There you go.  Now don't mortgage it.  You wo
n't get anything from this.  [laughter]
Brother, he
said such nice things about you.  I want you to
also tell me about Manju ji.
What are your favorite one or two qualities about them?
No, of all the people who have come into my life
, the most lovely ones were the girls.  The
sweetest thing besides this is dirty praise.   I am
saying this to praise you, yes you are saying this,
before this I had many girls.
Meaning it is the best at that time.   She
neither doubts nor gets angry.  And the current
situation is such that today's girls do not
doubt anything good.  Yes.  She doesn't doubt it, does she?
[laughs]
So your previous girlfriend was very suspicious of you
?
Yes.  Are?
Well, Manju, you never doubted him?
No, I have never done it with anyone.
No, is his nature very good?
My condition is bad right now.  But nowadays girls would
leave it.  The situation that is going on right now.  But
she is always there and still speaks.
You have mortgaged it, brother.  [laughs]
And how will she leave from home, brother?  She
wants to run away from home.  [ __ ]' pawned the stuff
[laughs] this guy, man.  I do
n't have any of this stuff.
It's for a reason, man.   No no, it is not like that.
Is very lovely.
You guys definitely
didi also likes you.  Meaning, it is kept very well.   That's
very true, friend.
A big round of applause for Vijendra Bhai, friend.  Thank you sir.   Thank
you.  [Applause]
Time to score Vijendra Rajak bhai.  May you
start from Rahul Dua.
Brother, I want to give you 10 out of 10 marks.
For your acting,
for your personality and for your cute couple
dynamics, it was a lot of fun meeting you.
Brother, I have given 10 marks for both of you, 10
extra marks for you.
Okay, thank you.
I give eight so that there is some balance.
Good average too at
10 yes I will give nine.
Brother, I give you 10 on 10.  I really
like you both man.   Yes
sir.
What if he gave himself 10, who
knows?
That makes your average.  9.5
ohms.
Oh no.
I am thinking of changing my
score.
What brother,
what is it
brother,
first it came to my mind that I should give you 9.5,
I said I will give you nine
because you did not win, we wanted you to win,
I want you to go out more, not just
malls, you can also travel in India, so on
behalf of District I am giving you
50000 District points 50000,
so you can go to any restaurant in
District and have food for ₹00,
anytime that you want, let's go, thank you so much
for joining
Vijendra Bhai [praise]
I love you all the best Hey brother
[music]
He is teasing Tanmay Butt.
[laughter]
[music]
Wow, oh
my god,
sir, the waist is missing, brother, I feel like
eating noodles inside this,
my
brother, give him some protein [music]
he needs it, take it from him, sisterfucker, he will not do it on the
table.
Okay, hey, let's go, let's go
[encouraging voice]
brother, he's having a really bad day today.
Fun
brother, you are my security.  You are losing
to anyone anyway.  [laughter]
Karan Ojala brother.
Yes sir.
How did you like his body?
No meaning.
No, I mean speak carefully brother.  Have
you seen his body?
No brother, he is flexing properly.  What do I
mean now?
You are also flexing.  Look at the watch, it is worth Rs 5
crore.
[Encouraging voice]
Brother, you also do it like this.  [laughs]
Brother, if you don't like any of my jokes
, throw a watch in my face.
[laughter]
Dude,
if your mood gets worse, you should
immediately throw me out of here. [laughter]
Throw him in your private [laughter] I can't hear him from here.
And
Deep Gopal Lokhande, what you've done is right. I
mean, it's
right to do all this. Getting naked
in public in public is okay. If I
'm 18 plus, it's okay. I guess I'm 18 plus,
so you'll
roam around naked. 18 plus, half naked,
half negative.
This is not right, brother. Brother, you
flex so hard. Sometimes the nude gets on like this. I
mean [laughter] When the train overflows, the
police.
Hello friends, the lights went out in the middle of the show.
Brother, what nudity did you see?
[laughter] The
lights will be ashamed.
What a scene with the lights. Tushar,
another show.
Oh, it won't come. If we stop here,
it's Mumbai City. Dude
also gave it a try.
[encouraging voice]
Check, check,
brother. I was making fun of your show so much.
[laughter]
Sorry brother.
[cheering]
What is this?  This Flipkart arrived
so quickly.
[Encouraging voice]
Friends, the lights may go but brand integration should not
go.
Here you go friend.  This is Veer Biceps High.
Yes good.
[Applause]
Paji one or two songs.
[Cheering voice]
Who is sitting there?
Show me his face.  Who is it?  Who is it?
Your [cheering voice]
mic is working.
Okay, will you sing along with me?  Which
boyfriend should I sing?
Boyfriend
Saathsa Tere Ko Sing Naagi.
Come come brother, come come come.
[applause] Wow.
[Encouraging voice]
You're getting quite strong.  Let's start with the boyfriend first.
Come on brother, let's beat everyone.  Okay, no one,
I will sing it like this brother.   It's done
[screaming] It's done
Someone went someone
took away [cheering voice] He took away
Someone went and took away
from Hariya
What's the matter What's the matter What's the matter Okay okay
[cheering voice]
I too needed it in the end
Okay okay okay okay okay
tell me one more village
[cheering voice] Will you
sing along [screaming voice] No, whoever you are, I didn't cast an evil
eye on you I don't know about your
pride I don't know about yours I don't know what's the matter
friend
all the girls' songs are on the air Thank you friend Thank you so
much
Okay let's go down and freshen up a bit
15 minutes
Yes brother let's go
Okay will yes
one second first let them leave then we will I will I will
manage the crowd you guys go down just like
15 minutes
while scenes
Okay see if Millers is open we can drink down
until then
Millers Mill it is so a one second one
second a
I am sure we can afford it drinks on
time
[cheering  [Encouraging voice]
So let's but but but listen
line by line let's go here yes
actually or start from the back
[Encouraging voice]
One by one one by one slowly slowly slowly
drinks I will come I will come I will join you guys I join you guys
sister [ __ ] he is saying give me food also brother
[laughter]
Friends till the lights come back in the habitat
I have come to tell you something very important if
you are watching the latest at home.  You are doing very
well.  But the real fun of latent
is in watching it live sitting in this room.
See, anything can happen.  Sometimes the lights go out,
sometimes we dance, sometimes we laugh, sometimes
we cry.  That happens after the episode is released.
But if you want to
experience all this while sitting in your room, then here is the
QR code.  You can scan this
and you can be part of all my life shows
including my India tour, my world
tour and latent life.  So this is a QR code.
Scan Your Tickets and Scan this
QR Code and Get Your Tickets Right Now.
Just like that Karan was doing the same show again.
What's up friend?  Bring back the naked man.
Come sisterfucker, Deep Gopal, come back friend.   I have arrived.
Come brother.
Brother, how much time did it take you to build such a body
?
I have been continuing my workout for four years.
And what do you do for protein?
[laughter]
You eat Muscle Bleus, right?  Avatar avatar
avatar avatar.   Have
you tried the Hold Truth protein bar?
Avatar avatar avatar avatar.  [laughter]
Super you, right?  Sisterfucker friend.  A brand has come with
great difficulty, friend.  So
how do you like the Avatar Protein?   I
mean I have tried it, of course top
quality but very high budget.
How much is this?   Is
anything too high budget for you?   No no,
still.
How much is it?  ₹120.
Then why did you give me the 80 one?
[laughs]
Okay, this one, sorry, sorry, ok
brother, get your drink too, friend, please,
he also started a drink recently
with Virat Kohli,
oh let's go, he has done
clothing with Virat Kohli,
I made this drink myself, ok, ok
[laughs] sometimes you say Diljit to me,
sometimes ok, ok, no,
you started it,
see, all this is average, ok, this zero
sugar, if you want to take care of yourself, then cut down on sugar.
And the test in this is also zero by the way.
So Rahul is coming from zero on a world
tour soon [cheering voice] may be if
you can give a shout out to your
world tour friend.
Or did someone confiscate my passport?
[laughter]
Brother, there's nothing like that, brother.
For one hour really good humor good
[cheering voice]
[applause]
Rahul I love you man.
Written here I Had So Many Weird Grey
Interactions.  I love your lips.  [laughs] I
mean, there are a lot of weird people on Instagram.
I want you.  I want yours.
Such things keep coming.
[Cheering voice] Here comes the
DM.
Hey friend, I had messaged you privately, you
sisterfucker.  Why are you telling
everyone publicly [laughs], friend?  I was talking to you with such love, friend.
You have written here that I am really good
at making bad and unfunny jokes.  Why do
you do this?
Or it happens to you.   It happens,
meaning whatever happens, happens
with the close one.   It happens sometimes.   It will become
one.
You still have it on your heart before the lights go out.
Tell me one.  Tell me one, unfinished.
Tell me one friend, should I
tell you one?  My friend and I were just talking on the
call.  So he was saying that I
bought this for Rs 5,000, I bought this for Rs 10,000.  I was
telling it like this.  So I said why do you want to
buy all this brother what is it like that he says that
he does it just for fun brother then
I said brother you should go and touch the current it was
dirty I mean I know it was dirty
oh my god [laughs]
to heal from true jokes go to Rahul show
for much better comedy
for much much better comedy
brother when this light went off my whole body changed
[laughs]
love you Samay bhai love you Samay
love you too friend come on man Deep bhai I have a question
yes yes you have written here that I am
currently on a more than 100 day no fab
streak it has been
100 days for you more than
brother last time a guy did no fab right
[laughter]
[encouraging voice]
why why are you doing this no fab 100
days streak
means I had become kind of addicted to that
thing so then I had to change it ki it
also has protein something like that
[laughter]
paaji Karan paaji yaar
I  I won't say anything about it
[laughter]
but you do all this, my
brother needs a little, my
brother needs it a lot [laughter] come,
I'll do it, then
I'm married, my brother, it's okay,
brother, we'll both turn off the camera [laughter]
so it's written here, what else is written here,
brother, ask, Tanu Bhai, you ask, you're also
asking the right question,
brother,
ask the drug dealer,
okay, ask the drug trafficker, yes, he'll
keep it on the edit, right [laughter]
brother, so which drug do you like, friend,
sorry, friend, they
ask like this, sorry, sorry, let me
tell you how to ask, the cyber cell will also
look into this, you've written a very bad thing here
[laughter]
[encouraging voice]
[applause]
if you could get away with one crime, it would be
drug trafficking, seriously, man, I mean, it
was inspired by Breaking Bad, I mean, it would be a bit
thrilling,
it's not correct
[laughter] I mean, it's not right, and which
crime do you commit, it's wrong, drugs, yes, yes, have
you ever done it?
Never of course never then
why do you want to do drug trafficking I mean right now which
crime do I write, I don't write murder of course
well if one murder is legal then you have
one murder
Ranveer Allahabad [laughs]
hey friend
[encouraging voice]
no friend come on man he
thought about his death [laughs]
[encouraging voice]
sweet sung man come on because of him so many
sponsors have come in this season shout out to
my man Ranveeriya
[encouraging voice]
65 million views
brother it was fun watching you both brothers come back
in one year of controversy
[laughs]
learn something.
[Applause]
Alright time to score this guy who I want
to score later.
Brother, I want to give you number nine.   This is the
first time I've given numbers to someone's naked body.
[laughter]
Number nine, thank you.  Thank you.
Why have you cut one?  By looking at the nipple.
[laughter] That's
eight numbers from me.  At Numbers.
Why cut two numbers?  One for each nipple
[laughs]
One for each nipple.
Paaji, I will give you six marks.
Why are you cutting six and four marks, brother?
I have not come here to see this, brother.
[laughter] Come on man.
Sorry friend.
And if everyone had given 10, his 100 days tree would have been
finished brother.  [laughs] I
really found you very attractive.  Thank
you.  Thank you.
I give it to you.
[laughter]
No, man, don't do this.   That's
it.
[laughter]
Later, definitely
I want to give you that's pretty much it, I don't know.
[laughter]
So I'll give you a
10, man.
[applause]
So that makes your average 8.5,
nine, nine?  Nice [ __ ] man [ __ ] they're so close just like I was when I saw you said
man it's fun Deep Gopal thank you so much I
wish you one more [cheering voice]
[applause]
all right
[laughter]
all right make some next Gaurav Madan
[applause]
it's gonna do some stand up comedy with the
guitar.
Brother, the previous one took away all the muscle.
[laughter]
[cheering]
Guys for real amazing comedy goal show
my [cheering] man touring all across
the world.
I love you Rahul Bhai.
You too brother.   He has been
beating me every day for the last 100 days.  [laughs] He has a
different streak going on, Paaji.  I
also took a break for a day in between.  Guys let's have
a round of applause for Gaurav Madan Yaar.   Let's
go.  Let's go.  Let's go.  [Praise]
I have been going to the gym regularly for six years.
[laughter] That wasn't a joke, brother.  No, I am actually
going to the gym and in my gym I
recently heard a song.  The lyrics of that song
were Luck 28 Kudida 47 Wait Kudida.
Right?  Its meaning is basically that the girl
's waist size is 28 and her weight is 47.
Right?  While listening to this song, I realized
that my measurement is also the same.  [laughs]
[laughs] I have the perfect body for a
Punjabi supermodel.
But I have written this song about going to the gym like this.
You people have heard that song of Arijit Singh ji,
Khamoshiyan.   You wo
n't be able to hear it after today.  Sorry it goes
like [nasal voice] I
did leg day tomorrow evening Now I will
[song voice] I find
my trainer standing there He's a monster I'll strangle him
desperately [song voice]
Every body part needs rest
Weakness
[encouraging voice]
Weaknesses
are in the legs
[applause]
Weaknesses are in the thighs Did
your pajamas get stuck in those machines
[laughter] I had to
lie down and get my legs stuck I went to
drink water someone brought a dumbbell Should I
tell you what all happened to me I've
also taken magnesium I've started eating omega three
[song voice] [
music] [encouraging voice] [
encouraging voice]
[applause]
I used to be a vegetarian Now I boil eggs in the morning
Protein intake
[song voice] [music] It wasn't complete
but my digestion improved
[music]
[encouraging voice] Weaknesses
[music] Weaknesses are
in the thighs.
[Soundbite of singing]
[Music]
Thank [Soundbite of cheering] you.
[Applause]
Open, open, open, open, quickly, quickly.
Oh my God.
What
[applause] oh [ __ ] bro.  What a rockstar I was,
I have written it from my heart, friend. I
cannot write it with my fists [laughs]. Since
when have you been doing this,
I wrote this song only six months
ago. I have been doing stand-up for five or six years.
What's the matter, friend, you have written here that you have done 100
days challenge.
100 days 100 push-ups challenge. I used to do one
push-up daily [laughter]
[encouraging voice] [applause]
Well Gaurav Bhai, do you want to gain weight?
Offcourse yes.
So maybe you can give him some advice, friend.
No, I want to ask Tanmay Bhai whether the
fat you lost is kept somewhere
?  [laughter]
[encouraging voice]
That's right Baba.
Brother, what is your weight?
It is kept in the mouth of Kullu.
[Cheering voice]
You have your opinion: We should remove mirrors
from changing rooms.
Yes, I mean because when I go to the changing room to
try some clothes.
Right, sometimes I don't want to
see myself fully nude.
Right?  Just recently I went there and I
saw myself completely naked.  Meaning that's
okay bro.
I had gone to buy shoes.  [laughter]
So why did you get completely naked then?
That was the joke
[cheering voice]
revenge is coming today.  Damn bro it's written here
if you could travel back in time you would
practice removing a bra.
So you have a girlfriend?
No, not right now.
Was it good before?   Yes.
So obviously you guys must have actually gone
for it.  Go for it.  [laughter] There's
something in the [ __ ] chair.
Something is really going on.  [laughter] It's just a few
chickens coming in every now and then.  Put something.  Pari,
you are asking whether you ever
created an atmosphere for a baby or not?  As such.
Meaning obviously you guys were a couple.  How
serious was your relationship?  I mean six to
seven months,
yes that's right, so what was your experience like, I mean did you guys have any [ __ ], that's where I'm going
[laughs]
Gullu Gullu is
not there, that was my finger, friend [
laughs]
[appreciation]
brother, you can also keep the guitar if it's becoming too heavy
[laughs]
Gullin got tired after seeing that, friend.  [laughs]
Who brother, here you said that if you could
switch lives with someone for a day it would be
Hrithik Roshan from Koi Mil Gaya.
Yes, actually many people tell me that
my voice sounds a bit like Hrithik.
But he says that the first half
sounds like Hrithik Roshan [laughs].  So I want
you to say Bonavita in the second half.
Bonavita [laughs]
[cheering]
you sick bro like actually [laughs] [cheering
]
[applause]
alright man time to score Gaurav Madan you are
[ __ ] incredible man I give you 10 on 10
brother 10 on 10 from
me man 10 on 10 with this guy
10 10 from Tanmay
Kulan
10 oh no that makes
your average 10 come
on man
[cheering]
[music]
what a guy bro I love you man I will give you a hug
man come on man
[cheering] thank you man it was
very right man
wow bro you are so funny you win the whole ticket
prize that's ₹1 lakh my brother
take the medicine now ok [laughs]
you know what man you know what's missing in
your that's some good protein.
I give you today only for today.  I'm gonna
make an exception.  Every time people come in I
give them a protein bar.  I'll give you this
milkshake.  I give you from
Avatar.
₹ lakh [sound of clearing throat] worth of
protein my brother.  There you go.
[Cheering]
There you go brother.  5 lakh worth of protein
to you.  [cheering] There you go
?
So what will you do now with protein worth Rs. lakh?   I
will [ __ ] my digestion.  [laughter]
[applause]
[cheering] There you go, my
brother.  Thank you so much for coming and giving
your talent to our show.  Big applause for
this guy man.  Thank you.  Thank you so much.
And that was India's God Lin.
[cheering]
Thank you so much.  Karan Bhai, tell me the truth.  How was
your experience of the?
Bro.  I felt like I was home and I
feel like I was being a little too frank.
[laughs] I do
n't know if this is the right decision or the wrong
decision.  But I am enjoying it a lot brother,
wow.  Karun Bhai, if you have already felt at
home then next time it
breaks down then the cost of renovation will be there.  [laughter]
A little atmosphere you.   On
this very note friends, Rahul Dua is on tour.
You can go to his show and my show We're Both
on Tour.  Gullin is also on tour.
Accept on my Everybody on Tour.
Tanmay
I am working on my
computer Tanmay [laughter]
[screaming voice]
You are making the same noise at cyber cell
master
[encouraging voice]
[music]
This is what is
in your eyes It is in my tea
pot Everyone's eyes are on you
You shake your mood [music] I will shake the
floor Say it in my ears Baby [music] Let's let it thump a
little more today My
heart beats come come don't stop
[music] You give signals from your eyes Do it again
[music] [music] [music]
[music]